couponroller.com 2016-11-26

# privacy policy coupon

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Coupon Roller LLC collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the [http://www.couponroller.com](http://www.couponroller.com/) Website ("Website"). This privacy policy applies to the Website and all products and services offered by Coupon Roller LLC.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Website, register on the Website, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Website. Users may be asked for their e-mail address. Users may, however, choose to visit our Website anonymously. They Website reserves the right to offer a different experience to anonymous users than to users who have registered. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Website related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Website. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Website, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized, Internet Protocol addresses and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Website may use "cookies" to enhance the user experience. The User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Website may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Coupon Roller LLC may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * \- To improve customer service  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * \- To personalize user experience  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Website.
  * \- To send periodic emails  
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they may receive emails that include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or, alternatively, the User may contact us via our Website.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Website, per industry standards.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined herein. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Website or administer activities on our behalf, such as, but not limited to, sending out e-mail. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

**Third party Websites**

The Website reserves the right to include Advertising or other content on our Website that link to the Websites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. Note that we do not control the content or links that appear on these Websites and therefore we are not responsible for the practices employed by Websites linked to or from our Website. In addition, these Websites or services, including their content and links, are likely to be dynamic and hence will be constantly changing. These Websites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies, and you are encouranged to learn about them. Browsing and interaction on any other Website, including Websites which have a link to or from our Website, is subject to that Website's own terms and policies, and not to ours.

**Advertisers**

Ads appearing on our Website may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, or third-parties of any kind, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Coupon Roller LLC has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect any personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy page periodically in order to become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Website, you indicate your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, you are asked to not use our Website. Your continued use of the Website following any changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of said changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with this Website, please contact us at:  
2885 Sanford Ave SW #13307 Grandville, MI 49418  
786-405-0763  
support@couponroller.com

This document was last updated on June 14, 2014
